[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":38931,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":54799,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":8729,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":63529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":9305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":72836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3094,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":75931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5353,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":81286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1518,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":82805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one t o it. If  the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":11331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":94137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1293,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":95431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5632,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":101064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":992,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":102056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3862,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":105919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0  = 3 bec ause 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1183,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":107104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3074,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":110179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1129,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":111309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> ( Remember , to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":6265,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":117575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1143,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":118720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":121480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1926,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":123407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":126192,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":783,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":126976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2827,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":129804,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":973,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":130778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":20308,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":151088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under  +<sub>6< /sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":24249,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":175339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":183707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":22035,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":205744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub >? <br / ><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":10209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":215955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":216964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":219907,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1611,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":221518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":224209,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the ident ity unde r +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1088,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":225298,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":6058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":231357,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2588,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":233946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation  can simp ly be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":19205,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":253152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<s ub>6</su b> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":31373,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":284528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":8624,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":293153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1493,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":294647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br / > (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3719,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":298367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":5061,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":303429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub >6</sub> ? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":306540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1167,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":307707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5312,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":313020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":4887,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":317908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice quest ion with  feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19445,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":337354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4821,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":342176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1288,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":343465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2618,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":346084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":350434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":352660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":355545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":358046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":11925,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":369972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0 "},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem  is complete ","explanation_history":["since 4 plus 2","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine  ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine it is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine i is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine  is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine t is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine th is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the  is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the p is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the pr is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the pro is complete "," since 4  plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the prob is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the probl is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the proble is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem  is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem i is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem is is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem is  is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem is is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem i is complete ","since 4 plus 1 is 5 which is less than nine the problem  is complete "],"response_history":["5"],"rt":55747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":425720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please expla in in wo rds how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"eight plus four is 12 so before it is complete you must subtract 9. ","explanation_history":["eight plus four is 12 so before ","eight plus four is 12 so before","eight plus four is 12 so befor","eight plus four is 12 so befo","eight plus four is 12 so before it is complete you must subtract 9 ","eight plus four is 12 so before it is complete you must subtract 9. "],"response_history":["3"],"rt":46430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":472151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"it would be the same as +6","explanation_history":["it would be the same as +6 ","it would be the same as  +6"],"response_history":["9","0"],"rt":83209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":555362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":14521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":569884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":5917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":575802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":579393,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"you would take the number given and subtract it from 9 because you are trying to find the 0 identifyer ","explanation_history":["you would take the number given and sup","you would take the number given and subtract it from n","you would take the number given and subtract it from 9 because you are trying to find the 0 identifyer ","you would take the number given and subtract it from 9 because you are trying to find the 0 identifyer "],"response_history":["6"],"rt":34247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":613640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"yea because you can add numbers to it to get any number under 9 ","explanation_history":["yea because you can add ","yea because you can add 2 and ","yea because you can add 2 and","yea because you can add 2 an","yea because you can add 2 a","yea because you can add 2 ","yea because you can add 2","yea because you can add ","yea because you can add","yea because you can ad","yea because you can a","yea because you can sub trac","yea because you can sub tra","yea because you can sub tr","yea because you can sub t","yea because you can sub ","yea because you can sub","yea because you can su","yea because you can s","yea because you can numbers to ","yea because you can numbers to","yea because you can numbers t","yea be cause you can numbers to it to get any number under 9 ","yea because you can  numbers to it to get any number under 9 ","yea because you can a numbers to it to get any number under 9 ","yea because you can ad numbers to it to get any number under 9 ","yea because you can add numbers to it to get any number under 9 "],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":57323,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":670964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"i really don't get the generator, yes because i think because you might beable to get all the numbers added to make 9 ","explanation_history":["i really dont get the generator ","i really dont get the generator, yes because ","i really don't get the generator, yes because i think becau se you m ight beable to fget","i really don't get the generator, yes because i think because you might beable to fge","i really don't get the generator, yes because i think because you might beable to fg","i really don't get the generator, yes because i think because you might beable to f","i really don't get the generator, yes because i think because you might beable to get all the numbers added to make 9 ","i really don't get the generator, yes because i think because you might beable to get all the numbers added to make 9 "],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":65203,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":736168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no because you can't get 2 or 1 by adding 5 to anything ","explanation_history":["n o because you can't a","no because you can't get 2 or 1 by adding 5 to d","no because you can't get 2 or 1 by adding 5 to anything "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":27338,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":763507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no because you can't get a 1 2 by adding anything ","explanation_history":["no because you can't get a 1 ","no because you can't get a 1 2 or 3 ","no because you can't get a 1 2 or 3","no because you can't get a 1 2 or ","no because you can't get a 1 2 or","no because you can't get a 1 2 o","no because you can't get a 1 2 by adding anything "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":26308,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":789816,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":14242,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":804059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"N-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["N-1"],"rt":17259,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":821319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how yo u got yo ur answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x ","explain":true,"explanation":"to find the inverse you would subtract n from the element x ","explanation_history":["to find the inverse you would sub","to find the inverse you would subtrack","to find the inverse you would subtract ","to find the inverse you would subtract n from the  x","to find the inverse you would subtract n from the  ","to find the inverse you would subtract n from the element x "],"response_history":["n-x "],"rt":50979,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":872299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because I'm not sure ","explain":false,"explanation":" ","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no because I'm not sure "],"rt":47097,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":919397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":6934,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":926334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":7045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":933379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":35243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":968623,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"you have to be able to divide by the number so yes","explanation_history":["you h","you have to be able to try ","you have to be able to try","you have to be able to tr","you have to  be able  to t","you have to be able to divid by the number so yes ","you have to be able to divid by the number so yes","you have to be able to divide by the number so yes"],"response_history":["True"],"rt":42304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1010928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":16802,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1027731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got  your ans wer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"there would be over lap some numbers would have to be the same ","explanation_history":["there would be over lap so ","there would be over lap some numbers would have to be the same "],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":40251,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1067983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":15101,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1083085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14- 0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2122,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1085210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["32"],"rt":2179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1087389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3366,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1090756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College intro to calculus ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["College algerbra ","College algebra ","College intro to calculus "],"rt":31342,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1122100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it,  remember  and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1127498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":5133,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1132632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned s omething  from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1136655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1140108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2  - somewh at","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1142461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2720,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1145181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["english"],"rt":15267,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1160449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":10587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1171037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"thank you but I got really confused ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["thank you buyt ","thank you buyt","thank you buy","thank you buy ","thank you buy","thank you buy ","thank you buy","thank you but u","thank you but I got really confused "],"rt":31698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1202736,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]